## ARDIKA VALDAN KAFACHRY

+62 814 5910 7624 | +62 882 2365 6959 | ardikavaldan850@gmail.com

Linkedin : Ardika Valdan | Instagram : @ardikavaldan



#### **ABOUT ME**

Graduated with a Bachelor's degree in Civil Engineering from Muhammadiyah University of Yogyakarta with a GPA of 3.45 and good English language skills. Possesses expertise in construction project management, project supervision, and construction project planning. Experienced in organizational activities, has strong leadership qualities, can easily adapt to work environments, and has good time management skills.

#### **EDUCATION**

## MUHAMMADIYAH UNIVERSITY OF YOGYAKARTA – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Bachelor of Civil Engineering – 3.45 GPA (2020-2024)

- Member of the Student Executive Board of the Faculty of Engineering for the year 2021-2022
- Public Relations Coordinator for the Social Affairs and Cooperation Division of the Student Executive Board of the Faculty of Engineering Muhammadiyah University of Yogyakarta, for the year 2021-2022
- Member of the Civil Engineering Student Association (HMS)

#### SMAN 3 TARUNA ANGKASA MADIUN - Madiun, Indonesia

Science – Final Grade 86.20/100.00 (2017-2020)

- Vice Chair of the Flag Hoisting Troops (Paskibra) Organization in 2019
- 4th Place and Public Relations for the School's Cultural Ambassador in 2018

#### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

## PT. UNISYSTEM UTAMA – Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Project Supervision Intern (Aug 2023-Sep 2023)

- Responsible for overseeing and documenting work on building construction projects
- Conduct quality inspections of building construction
- Prepare daily progress reports for building construction projects

#### ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

# PAGUYUBAN KAKANG MBAKYU DUTA WISATA KOTA MADIUN – Madiun, Indonesia

Tourism Ambassador of Madiun City (2018-Now)

- Collaborated with the Department of Culture, Youth, Tourism, and Sports of Madiun City to organize activities aimed at increasing visitor numbers to over 1,000 tourists
- Promoted tourism through social media and other media channels to reach tourists

## BADAN EKSEKUTIF MAHASISWA FAKULTAS TEKNIK - Yogyakata, Indonesia

Coordinator of Relations and Cooperation with External Organizations (2021-2022)

- Acted as a liaison for the Faculty of Engineering students in social activities, such as organizing social events.
- Collaborated with more than 10 external organizations.

## HIMPUNAN MAHASISWA SIPIL UMY - Yogyakarta, Indonesia

Master of Ceremony MATAF SIPIL 2021

- Organized orientation events for more than 200 new students
- Provided information about the major to new students

## **CERTIFICATE**

### **TOEFL**

ITP Grade 512 (Dec 2023)

#### **OTHERS**

**Self Qualification**: Diligent, Communicative, Adaptive, Disciplined, Responsible **Hard skill**: Ms. Word, Ms. Excel, Ms. Power Point, Ms. Project, SAP2000, AutoCAD

Language: Bahasa Indonesia (fluent), English (casual)